[{"answer": "Right, I got news. You ready?  my friend had cancer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You knew? How did you know", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You knew? How did you know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Why did he tell you and not me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He told me a few months ago", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So, is he okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Huh, really? How bad? Was he on his death bed", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, he's fine, fine. He was in bad shape for a while though", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No, he was on his regular bed", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You don't think I can keep a secret", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You don't trust my poker face", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, but he would've read your face", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Do you ever win at poker", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well frankly, you can't keep a secret. You know, you'd get two pair, the whole table knows", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Right, well I'm sorry, all right. I guess I was just thinking of myself", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah, isn't that just like him?  You know, he has to be the only one who has 'em", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What?  You told my friend said hi", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No. Nothing. Fine.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "My regular face", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What are you saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I got nothing", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "All right my friend, c'mon, what d'you got?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What you got, a pair of bullets", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "So you see, my friend took it upon himself to say hi to you from me. When in fact it was an unauthorised hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "That's what I'm saying", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, I could do it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why didn't he tell me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't think I can be that nice", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You look like a pirate", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " This is my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, well, uh. my friend told me you said hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You didn't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I didn't say hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Uh, no. I told him to send you my regards. I didn't say hi", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Uh, no. I told him to send you my regards. I didn't say hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yeah, regards.", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Uh. Ah, if you don't mind my asking, could you tell me where you got your glasses", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "So, you didn't think this was a date", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I thought it was a date", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "N... no, not really. Why, is it... a date", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No. It's not a date", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Well, what d'you think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Scofflaw.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No, say. I want you to say", "qsentId": 46}]